#### Contact

khananamta876@gmail.com 9639649422 LinkedIn Profile

## Top Skills · See all

Hospital Operations · Data Mining · Strategic Planning · Quality Patient Care · Data Entry · Data Analysis · Event Management · Change Management · Customer Relationship Management (CRM) · Business Analysis

Accomplishments · See all

2 Certifications

# **Anamta Khan**

M.H.A, L.L.B- Criminal justice/Law Enforcement Administration(persuing)

New Delhi, Delhi, India

## Summary

A Highly dedicated, Self-motivated professional! Having served in Hospital & Healthcare industry, Customer service, Management, experienced in working IT Healthcare. e.g.-MICROSOFT as Business vendors. Competencies Training (Teaching), grooming, mentoring students at seniour secondary level. Experienced in start-up Operations and developing new Business areas. R...

## Experience

Summer Intern · Sanjay Gandhi Postgraduate Institute of Medical Sciences June 2017 - August 2017 (3 months) · Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh, India

### Science Trainer · Eminent Coaching Classes

April 2014 - July 2016 (2 years 4 months) · Moradabad, Uttar Pradesh, India

#### Education

## Chaudhary Charan Singh University

L.L.B , Criminal Justice/Law Enforcement Administration · (2019 - 2022)